CASINO
HEOYOUNG LAND ONE YEAR ANNIVERSARY
MANAGER BONG-CHEON KIM
ACTIVATE VOICE RECOGNITION
YOU ARE INVITED TO THE ONE YEAR ANNIVERSARY PARTY -
HEOYOUNG LAND'S…
DATE: TUESDAY, 8 April 2025, 10 PM.
VENUE: HEOYOUNG LAND CASINO
VVIP GAME ROOM, 5TH FLOOR
SEND
FOR VVIP MEMBERS ONLY
CASINO ONE YEAR CELEBRATION
APRIL 8, 2025, 10 PM.
Gold nuggets.
I'm the first.
When are the others coming?
A VVIP guest should not wait.
JEWELER AN
VVIP GUEST
My makeup is amazing.
I look twenty.
Good day.
Hello.
What brings you here, Singer?
This is not for you.
So.
SINGER KIM
REGULAR PERFORMERS
Isn't this for VVIP guests?
IS HE A VVIP?
Hello.
I've never been here.
KITCHEN MASTER JANG
You are the chef.
-So.
Why do we gather?
I wish you luck with today's card games.
The players have come.
Very nice to meet you.
Good day.
-Hello.
SEA CORP JANG
PLAYER OF THE HOUSE
It's embarrassing.
The players are there. Where is the dealer?
Is that the mayor?
What brings you here?
- Madam Mayor.
Good day everyone.
Have you been well?
MAYOR JEON
This is a surprise.
- You're fine.
Goodness.
AND YOU ARE…?
I didn't know the mayor's result.
-This is a big event.
Mrs. Mayor also came,
so this is a VVIP event.
Yukra.
Are you kidding me?
-Goodness.
Who coughs in the company?
-Hard cough.
Anyway…
Where is Bong-cheon?
Shouldn't he greet guests?
He should have come.
IS SOMEONE MISSING?
Please try to call.
-Where does he stay?
I have her number.
-So.
The main boss is usually not late.
A little moment.
Had he planned
something for us?
TRYING TO CALL HIM
He's here.
Where?
- The phone is ringing over there.
BEHIND THE CURTAINS?
Is he on stage?
He was planning some surprise.
It wouldn't have been necessary.
-Why doesn't he come out?
His number.
Oh no.
- Yukra!
Bong-cheon!
What the hell?
What the hell is this?
Blood!
-Oh no!
That's the boss!
MURDER OF THE CASINO BOSS I
CRIME SCENE ZERO
Oh no.
- Yukra!
Bonk-cheon!
What the hell?
What the hell is this?
What…
- Is that blood?
What is it about?
-Is this part of the show?
Boss?
- Bong-cheon?
THE MANAGER WAS FOUND DEAD ON STAGE
Are you okay?
-What is this?
Blood!
-Oh no!
What the hell?
Goodness.
Boss?
My heart is pounding.
What is it about?
-What the hell...
Guests are not treated this way.
-What?
My heart is pounding.
What is it about?
- Jukra.
What has happened?
- I have to go.
IS HE TRYING TO ESCAPE THE PLACE?
Where do you think you're going?
PRINCIPAL RESEARCHER
DETECTIVE PARK
Stand up.
- I want to go to the bathroom.
No, you're coming with me.
Move away. This is a crime scene.
Keys off.
First of all -
don't try to leave
or go near a corpse.
This is a murder scene.
Murder?
Was he murdered?
Currently -
you five are suspects.
What are you talking about?
- Are you kidding me?
We are not treated like this.
-I don't go to places like this.
You will soon understand why you are suspected.
Leave the stage to wait.
Get off the stage now.
I wouldn't bother killing.
- I'm busy.
I can't believe this. That for a big win.
Let's see.
Was he shot?
Those are gunshot wounds.
One on the head, one on the shoulder.
The victim died instantly,
and there are no signs of a struggle.
But your lips…
This looks like murder,
which was designed to be seen.
He is on stage in the VVIP arcade.
Detective.
-Hello.
I'm Minhee Kang, assistant sister.
Are you an AE?
-Yes.
You were recommended.
It is an honor to work with you.
-So.
What about the case file?
I have a victim -
and details of five suspects.
-Good.
You are at work for the last day.
Yes.
- You must be homesick.
Shall we start with the victim?
The victim is Bong-cheon Kim,
A 60-year-old man.
Asia's largest casino,
Heoyoung Landin, manager.
He is the godfather of the casino business.
The body was found on the stage of the VVIP game hall.
It was going to be held in the hall
the casino's one-year anniversary.
The cause of death is a gunshot wound to the head.
The time of death is last night
between 10pm and midnight.
That would mean
that the body has been here
almost 24 hours.
He was killed
at the casino's one-year anniversary,
at the biggest celebration of his career,
and was left to be seen.
Let's get started.
INVESTIGATION OF SUSPECTS
First suspect: Mayor Jeon.
A 42-year-old woman.
Mayor of Heoyoung Special City.
Second suspect: Jeweler An.
A 56-year-old woman.
Jewelry store owner
and the casino's VVIP customer.
Third suspect: Singer Kim.
A 43-year-old man.
Casino regular.
The fourth suspect: Chef Jang.
A 53-year-old man.
He is the special chef for VVIP customers.
The fifth suspect: Jang the cormorant.
A 48-year-old man.
A professional gambler hired by a casino.
You are now in a place,
where leader Bong-cheon Kim was killed.
First tell me,
why did you come here before me
As you know,
today was supposed to be a VVIP game.
It had to be big.
Really.
-What about the rest of you?
Bong-cheon invited me.
Were you close?
Let's leave it at that.
I didn't come to play or anything.
I got an invitation too.
I'm just doing my thing in the kitchen,
and I don't understand my invitation here.
It's weird.
They are not my usual opponents.
Please introduce yourself -
telling about your relationship with the deceased.
Let's start with you, Madam Mayor.
So I'm Mayor Jeon,
The mayor of Heoyoung.
So.
-You know me.
Is your father's mayor Four Seasons Jeon?
Really?
-They are known here.
You and your father are a well-known duo.
At Heoyoung Land Casino -
plays an important role in the life of our city,
because it attracts tourists
and boosts the local economy.
Bong-cheon Kim, from whom I received the invitation,
was important to me.
Did your partnership focus
for the development of the city?
Exactly.
- Or so.
What about his "friends"?
I am Jeweler An,
owner of a jewelry store.
You can hardly say that we were close.
When he asked for a favor, I agreed.
That's how it was.
You are not very young.
How long were you friends?
I don't look like that.
What?
-I was born in 1969.
They say I look twenty.
You didn't refuse
when he asked for a favor.
That's all there is to it.
Chef Jang.
I am Heoyoung Land's VVIP Kitchen Master,
who was recruited by the main boss himself.
"The main boss?"
-So.
You call him the main boss?
He's the best in Korea, isn't he?
Really?
-In the casino industry.
Do you cook for VVIP customers?
-Yes.
Only for them.
-Do you have Michelin stars?
The ones with excellent taste
don't care about such.
Have you been to Culinary Class Wars?
-A chef of my caliber -
does not participate in such.
-Clear.
Is that program below your level?
Is that not up to you?
So. I don't understand
the popularity of such programs.
You don't even understand their producers.
-So.
They are for untalented exams.
-Can you handle the consequences of that?
All right. We understand.
Are you also on the casino's payroll?
Singer Kim?
Yes, I'm Singer Kim.
- We know that.
Why are you coughing? Do you have a flu?
I've been singing a lot lately,
and my throat is too strained.
Are you employed by the casino?
Yes, I am a standard singer.
I have performed now
For VVIP and VIP guests.
VVIP customers worship him.
-Is he that good?
When he begins his performance,
everyone shouts: "Full on!"
The songs have such a strong impact.
Full on
Full on!
Players like us -
can't resist it.
Are you a gambler too?
I'm Jang the Seagull,
professional gambler and in-house player,
who was hired by the casino.
Where did you get that scar?
This one?
A dark past?
Everyone gets scars during life,
or what?
Did you get caught cheating?
- As if it would fit today.
Did you deal based on the deck?
Your hand is intact.
Doesn't that say something?
I'm not who you think I am.
My duty was to support the boss
and his casino with my skills,
and i did so.
All right.
I'll collect your alibi first
from the time of the murder,
but the body was not immediately found.
He was killed last night -
between 10pm and midnight.
-What?
The body lay here for almost a day,
so i ask what you did last night.
Madam Mayor.
I had a very busy day,
so I stayed late at the office.
Are you working long hours now?
Yes. My job is demanding.
Singer Kim?
-I returned to my room at 21:20.
I took the medicine and went to sleep.
-Clear.
I guess you had some time off, Chef?
Yes. I went to my room
after my shift is over.
How about you, Jeweler?
I played on the third floor.
-At the VIP table.
How about you, Sea Grouse?
I played until around 10.10pm -
and i went to my room.
Your timelines collide. Did you see each other?
I'm not sure. Did you see me?
Of course.
Did you see me?
-You played until a little past ten.
I don't remember seeing you.
The game requires concentration.
-Understandable.
Jeweler Ani's alibi has been confirmed
at least until 22:10,
but Merikrott was not seen.
That was all for now.
Someone is clearly lying,
and traces of the killer are found at the crime scene.
Look for evidence,
prove your theory right -
and identify the killer,
so that we can part amicably.
Shall we go?
Let's disperse.
I'm still shocked.
-I got hurt.
CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION
APRIL 8, 2025
CASINO ONE YEAR CELEBRATION
THE VICTIM WAS FOUND MURDERED ON THE STAGE
CASINO MANAGER BONG-CHEON KIM
HEOYOUNG LAND CASINO
STAGE, DRESSING ROOM
VVIP GAME ROOM, MANAGER'S WORK ROOM
THE SINGER'S ROOM,
KITCHEN'S ROOM
MERIKROTTI JANG'S ROOM
STAFF STATUS
JEWELRY STORE
MAYOR'S ROOM
CITY ARCHIVES
CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION
15 MIN IN PAIRS.
How long have you been a chef?
I was born with my gifts.
TEAM 2: MERICROTT & SINGER
What is it about?
I don't have time to dwell on this.
Will the body be examined?
-Sure.
INVESTIGATING THE BODY FIRST
How did the boss get here?
How can this happen?
Why is he on stage?
-Did he enjoy being on display?
And spotlights too.
Did he enjoy performing?
Does this remind you of Mint?
MONEY FORGE?
Or House of Cards?
TOWER OF CARDS
(I.E. HOUSE OF CARDS)
Was he shot?
-Really?
Isn't it a wound on the forehead
look like a gunshot wound?
He was shot twice.
On the shoulder and forehead.
The shooter was standing in front of him.
He had to be shot from the front…
Good time.
A larger exit wound confirms that.
Shouldn't there be shells?
Yes, because they pierced him.
What does that mean?
Did she wear lipstick?
No, that's not his style.
Maybe a kiss of death with closed lips?
Why would someone kiss after being shot twice?
Goodbye.
KISS GOODBYE?
What is this?
Why is the stomach swollen? Liquids?
Oh no.
-Let's check the pockets.
I found the phone.
BONG-CHEON KIM'S PHONE
Who is "Rude Little Shit"?
"Rude little shit."
-Really?
He was talking to one.
Let's see the messages.
"Rude little shit?"
-What?
Look at this.
RUDE LITTLE SHIT
"I already looked into it. What do you know? Obey."
(WHAT?)
"Is everything ready for the opening?"
"Vault..." "Yes, but I might not have time."
"The Truth Behind the Jeons."
This applies to you.
Jeon is a common surname.
-"The truth behind the Jeons."
Is there anything else there?
Messages to Secretary Kim.
-What?
"Go home already."
Wait a minute. "Duffer."
This…
-Who is Tohelo An?
Moment.
- I don't know.
Isn't your last name An?
"Tohello An."
MESSAGES TO TOHELO
“Bong-cheon, you know the CEO of Heaven Consortium.
We'll be right back. I want my regular table."
He was a regular.
He really was a tohelo.
SEA CORP JANG
"Tohelo is coming here."
"Okay. You can trust me."
A message to the Chef.
"Tomorrow is the one-year anniversary.
Special food."
"I make special food."
Something special?
SPECIAL FOOD?
DRESSING ROOM
Detective.
-So?
There is a gas warning.
And here are the instructions for the cleaners.
"Rules of Cleanliness."
“On the hill behind the casino
are often carcasses.
In summer they are filled with gas -
and can explode, so remove them."
Strange instructions for the cleaning team.
VVIP GAME ROOM
I'm a fool. Gotta check the phones.
This day was reserved for VVIP customers.
Truth be told -
just Mayor Jeon and me
we were worthy of the invitation.
i want to know
Did Bong-cheon invite the others too.
Who do you belong to?
Singer Kim, huh? You are suspicious.
"J Mail."
Same as the invitation I received.
ATTACHED TOKEN COUPON
WORTH 100,000,000 WON
Porcupine Jang -
and Jeweler An was also invited -
like me.
"V message bot?"
(SINGER'S PHONE)
What is this?
CALLING LIST CREATED BY ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
"I will not renew my contract with the casino."
"I'm going to Las Vegas to perform."
COME ON. TIME IS RUNNING OUT
Why didn't he wait a week?
...8. UNTIL THE DAY
STAFF FACILITIES
Those staying at the casino -
Merikrotti, Chef and Singer.
THE SINGER'S ROOM
Let's see, Singer Kim.
To Las Vegas?
You wanted to perform in the USA.
What is this?
Gifts from fans?
Mickey has his name on it.
Are these fan letters?
"Singer,
you drive me crazy with your screams."
“The voice of an angel.
You belong to a bigger stage.
Greetings, Wife Hwang."
He has admirers.
What's in the box?
The restaurant's account book.
"Mackerel."
"Income and Expenditure."
"Sea Grouse Jang's Fishery."
He was working at the fish market.
FRESH FISH
That's the Singer from before.
“You have the voice of a nightingale.
Who did you inherit it from?"
This is a family photo.
SINGER'S FAMILY PHOTO
“I will succeed
and I will give you a comfortable life."
"Pennies entertainment. Jin entertainment."
“You can be the next Jo Sung-mo.
All you need is 50 million won.”
Account book. This can be important.
Let's see.
THE SINGER'S ACCOUNT
"Boom Boom Karaoke,
everything possible..."
He toiled and sent the money
For the Pennitö entertainment company.
What?
“Dong Fertilizer Company.
FR. Tilizer's chemicals."
SUSPICIOUS BUSINESS CARDS?
What companies are these?
"Gazi's Adult Nightclub."
Did he perform there?
THE KING OF CATTLE SCREAMS
Am I too old for this?
ENVELOPE IN A TABLE BOX
"Employment contract of standard singer."
"September 1, 2024
and March 31, 2025.
Must perform all year round."
I examined the trash can.
There's something here.
"If you get caught, I'll shoot you."
Is that a gun?
Did someone threaten him?
I'm looking at the computer now.
SINGER KIM'S COMPUTER
"Messages."
From La Vega. "Singer, I was disappointed,
that you won't come to the audition."
(PICTURE ATTACHMENT?)
Talent scout from Las Vegas.
SCRIPT FROM EMAIL
"He doesn't audition."
I glance at Chef Jang's room.
CHEF JANG'S ROOM
"Feedback card."
"Splendid casino, premium meats."
"Sexy food."
He must be a good cook.
Isn't that a yoga mat?
This is used for meditation.
MEDITATION EQUIPMENT?
"Fleek Meditation Center."
MEDITATION CENTER
He likes to meditate.
"Director Cult Director Na.
Your message to the world."
"There is no more hope.
A new world is needed."
"The cause of my misery is Bong-cheon Kim?"
What is this?
We await that day.
Written by Cult Director Na.
He is clearly not sane.
“Listen, members of the Messianic Church.
Greed is the source of misery.
How to get rid of it?
A sacrifice must be offered."
A victim, huh?
How much did he really sacrifice for the cult?
The answer can be found in the account book.
He received the Four Seasons from Jeon
three billion won.
Isn't that Mayor Jeon's father?
He raised three billion
and established a clinic.
Is this guy a doctor?
Is there something? No.
A bag can be a gold mine.
KITCHEN BAG
Let's see.
What is this?
CLINIC BROCHURE
This is the Chef.
And my father.
What? He's actually a doctor.
Why is he a chef?
Wait a minute.
"The plaintiff, Celebrity Hong."
He had to pay five billion.
That's why he grinds.
Patient Oh's health information.
These are local people.
This person had a cold.
And the flu again.
Everyone had the flu.
You guys were up to something suspicious.
NEUROSURGERY - DOCTOR JANG
MERIKROTTI JANG'S ROOM
Staff status. Merikrot's room.
Jang the cormorant
was the closest leader with Kim,
so I wanted to research him.
What is this?
The official residence of the police?
Why are there women's clothes here?
A DRESS?
Does she cosplay?
What about in the box? And not.
"The Card Shark's Secret Handbook."
Being a card shark takes work.
"Otter, I don't know when I'll leave,
so you get my trade secret.”
Constable Hyeon?
"Mental strength.
Marking the cards."
There are enough techniques. "Distribution from under the deck.
A shuffling of cards."
What? "Fake clothes."
That accounts for it.
He dressed in fake costumes.
There's plenty to explore.
What is this?
It's heavy.
What is here?
There's a wig here.
Sunglasses.
Cards.
Wait a minute.
I don't know much about cards.
Is it easier to deal from under the deck?
Are these labeled?
(PUT ON GLASSES)
Goodness.
I was right. He's in trouble.
MARKS ARE VISIBLE WITH SPECIAL GLASSES
What kind of cream is this?
Why?
Why these tools?
This is used to mark objects.
He marked cards with this.
What is here?
Here is a photo.
Officer Hyeon must have died.
Are there bullet holes in the glasses?
“Constable Hyeon met last
By Bong-cheon Kim.
It must have been him.
He is a big sweat in the gambling world,
and the mayor protects him,
so it is difficult to continue the investigation."
This is where discoveries are made.
This is Constable Hyeon's notebook.
What's in this?
"I'm going to the city to play."
FOUR CONDITIONS JEON
BRIBERY AND DEGRADATION
"Hire the children of high officials..."
"Hosting the World Ball in 2002."
What a constable
and Merikrotti Jang's relationship is?
CITY ARCHIVES
THE BOX IS FOUND
Here's a scarf.
Women's scarf and hair clip.
How about this?
What? Was he in the fishing business?
MERIKROTTI JANG FISHERIES
He bought a fishing boat in 2001.
One mackerel, three mackerel,
two mackerel. Trade was slow.
A hundred mackerel?
In April 2002
he sold 100, 500, 300 and more.
2. APRIL
100 MACKEREL
APRIL 6
200 MACKEREL
APRIL 11
300 MACKEREL
I also glance at Mayor Jeon.
Excuse me, Madam Mayor.
MAYOR JEON'S WORK ROOM
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE ILO OLYMPIANS
MAYOR JEON
"Congratulations on getting 2036
joy olympics here."
CANDIDATE FOR 30TH MAYOR
POLITICIAN FATHER AND DAUGHTER
They look alike.
“I'll make sure you don't suffer a shortage
and you live comfortably."
Father developed a landfill.
"April 8th, Bong."
"Bong" again.
What did he do every 8 days?
"BONG" IS ALWAYS ON THE 8TH DAY
"Divine information,
written by Terä Myeong."
This is a notebook about Jeons.
"I advised the client to bury the victim
for a political career."
WRITTEN BY SHAMAN BLADE MYEONG
"A building shaped like a flower."
READY TO DESTROY BURIED SECRETS
"I advised to grow a bigger flower,
to become king."
IN A TABLE BOX
"Casino Development Agreement."
Let's see the pictures.
It looks like a flower.
"Grow a bigger flower..."
Is that why the casino was built there?
What is this?
"Will become king..." This is a prophecy.
“To become king
you have to grow a bigger flower on the grave."
Doesn't someone die if a grave is needed?
BOOKING AGREEMENT
"We are investigating the connections to Tuhokaupunki
to the landfill. Private Detective Jang.”
CLIENT: MAYOR JEON
(GOES THROUGH WALLS)
CITY ARCHIVES
1990s, 2000s…
ARCHIVED BY DECADE
From 2000, huh?
FINANCIAL PLAN OF THE CITY
THE YEAR 2000
LOSE 40 BILLION WON
"The dump." Now.
"Government subsidy money
coming to 80 billion won.
Landfill
is too close to populated areas,
but removing it from the report will help."
What happened after that?
LANDFILL APPROVAL
LANDFILL RELATED
The landfill has a secret.
JEWELRY STORE
What can be found here?
He is a VVIP customer of the casino,
so i want to know
why did he help Chairman Kim.
That's why I started a jewelry store.
Now.
What is here?
What is this?
When did you get such cards?
CARD SALE PROHIBITED
You can get everywhere with this.
Let's look at the cash.
What? "Ministry of the Interior."
Was he on state bread?
URBAN PLANNING
Can this be opened?
SAFE UNDER THE COUNTER
A SIX-DIGIT PIN?
I will try the number 690325.
THE TIME OF HIS BIRTH
I guessed.
Good time anyway.
Money, yes, but these others.
Let's see.
ENVELOPE FOUND
What is this?
Well, of course.
DEATH CERTIFICATE (AUTOMY REPORT)
"Rehti An. Died May 21, 2002."
Was the cause of death central nervous system trauma?
"The patient was injured in a run-over."
he died
because the surgery was too expensive. Oh no.
PHOTO IN THE ENVELOPE
“My dear little sister.
Let's live an honest and honest life."
The jeweler's older sister.
Something bad happened to Naispara.
What is this?
Written in 2002.
"Rehti, how will I manage without you?"
In 2006 he wrote:
“I found a clue about your death.
I'll get rich and make them pay."
From 2009:
"Honesty didn't go far."
From 2013.
I LIED ABOUT THE GOLD.
From 2018. He continued to commit illegalities.
Four Seasons something about Jeon.
DAUGHTER WILL BE MAYOR
He missed his sister.
"Mayor Jeon became mayor.
The daughter of our enemy."
What?
"That bastard. The gambling house."
"Every 7th of the month at 11pm."
What the hell? Wait a minute.
He hid this well.
BONG-CHEON KIM
OPPOSES FORCED TRANSFER
From 2002.
"After the landfill is completed
pollution worsened.
Pollution level -
exceeds the average of neighboring areas."
Lots of fish kills.
So there was something connected to the landfill.
"Citizens' group, represented by Rehti An."
"Black List of Forced Transfers in 2002."
Rehti An was on the black list.
Bong-cheon Kim did all kinds of shady stuff.
REHTI AN
BONG-CHEON KIM'S STUDY ROOM
That's too bad, boss.
You had money,
but you didn't have time to use them.
This is how he made his money.
"An Underwater Story." Yes, of course.
30. GAMBLING HOUSE
The 60th object of the gambling house.
Did he lead everything
With Mayor Jeon?
"Casino of Heoyoung Land."
Were they close?
"They play with high stakes."
LIST OF HIGH Stakes PLAYERS
They are really rich.
Could I get some of the boss boxes?
"Agreement."
Jeweler Ani had to cut
transfer subsidy at 80 percent -
and share the embezzled money with the boss.
The date changed from the 6th to the 11th.
I wonder why?
There's more here.
MOVE HUMBLE
AND BURY THE BAD HEADS IN THE LANDFILL
There's something down here.
"The zoning application for the commercial plot."
What?
What weld?
Was the casino going to be dismantled?
This too.
Wanted.
That's Merikrot.
“The catcher of this villain
get 50 million won.”
Discovery reward from Merikrot.
How did they get along?
WHY DID THE VILLAIN PLAY AT THE CASINO?
Here is the resume.
NAME: KITCHEN MASTER JANG
DOCTOR OF NEUROSURGERY
Why… When was this?
Did he run the clinic too?
What is this?
"Promissory note. Issuer: Bong-cheon Kim.
Creditor: Chef Jang.”
Did he borrow three billion?
Three billion won.
He had to act as a cook.
Despite the loan -
why clinic manager from Gangdam
worked in the kitchen?
TADAA
Good time.
Detective.
-So?
FOUND SOMETHING IMPORTANT?
What now?
I'm gathering as much evidence as possible.
Isn't that a button?
How did it end up there?
THE DOOR IS LOCKED
It works with sound.
But the leader is dead.
How to activate this?
Detective.
What now?
- It's time to go.
Think you can command?
Found anything?
There was so much information,
that I struggled with it.
DETECTIVE OFFICE
COMBINATION OF WIRE WIRES
I hope you tried
clear the doubts.
Was there any evidence?
How would a deck of cards like this be in a casino?
-You took the most pictures.
Speed ​​up.
-Much.
I put the rice on the fire.
Come on, Mr. Otter.
So?
- Let's start.
Shall I start?
-Please.
The perpetrator is recognized immediately.
Please.
First of all -
the cause of death is clear.
A shot straight to the forehead.
He was shot in the forehead and shoulder.
It is difficult to aim accurately with a gun,
so possibly -
he was shot at close range.
Maybe the killer shot the leader,
when this was lying down?
So.
-Singer Kim.
That is possible.
-I'm nailing it.
Chef Jang,
who left the rice to boil.
So?
I thought I'd come to you
when I want good food,
but it seems
that I come to you when I'm sick.
Chef Jang -
used to be a doctor.
He ran the clinic -
In Gangdam for 20 years.
No wonder.
-That's why white color suits him.
This is hard to understand.
He was a popular doctor,
which led
successful clinic for more than 20 years.
Why a three billion loan,
who forced him into the soup -
and to obey the lender
absolutely everything?
Life is short.
I wanted mine to be dynamic.
-Sure.
Thus thought
transitioning into a chef is not a shock.
Really?
I thought you were a genuine VVIP customer,
but I didn't realize your value.
Next is Korukauppias An.
He has a lot to talk about.
You have a VVIP card,
which can be accessed in this casino
just about anywhere.
Really?
The boss…
-You don't know how much I paid.
Maybe you noticed that he has
has deposits over 70 billion won.
73.4 billion.
You weren't born rich.
You have done some questionable work.
You have been selling cheap copies -
or gold-plated jewelry in gold.
You surely know -
extremely expensive
From the "Slime of the Sun" gem.
Worth billions?
- Seven billion won.
He smuggled it to China.
However, this is important.
Your older sister was Rehti An, right?
He got hit by a car,
and the driver fled the scene.
He died because of your family
could not afford surgery.
After your sister died -
you planned and saved
for more than 20 years -
for revenge.
This needs to be investigated.
I will surely miss seeing you
Mayor Jeon here.
Never mind.
- Me?
You say in your diary
Four Through Jeon as your sister's murderer.
My father wouldn't have done that.
You are mistaken.
-The daughter resembles her father.
Is this new, Mayor Jeon?
I didn't know about this.
-Is your father alive?
He is dead.
- Or so.
I'll turn this over to my boss.
Some notes
seemed to refer to him.
"Bastard" and game caves.
Nothing connects directly
his sister's death -
Four Ways to Jeon, Mayor to Jeon
or to today's sacrifice.
Not yet.
- We'll keep an eye on it.
Good job, Jang the Seagull.
-Thanks.
Jeweler An.
All right.
I'll tell you right now that I have
100 billion in funds.
You saved more than 70 billion in the casino.
70 percent of them were deposited here.
It's worth mentioning.
-Sure.
I started thinking
that the murder was a show.
-Yes.
The body was laid out for viewing.
I was puzzled,
that Singer Kim, Cormorant Jang -
and Chef Jang had been invited
For the event of VVIP customers.
Likewise.
-What if we -
was called after the murder
to prove -
this kind of show?
I have a question.
-Please.
Who did you get the invitation from?
From Bong-cheon?
-I got an email from the boss.
So.
-When?
That's the time this morning.
- Is it?
Likewise.
-What about you?
So the killer invited everyone
as the manager of the casino,
that ye may see the body.
-Exactly.
I'll start with singer Kim.
Do I?
I liked your childhood picture,
where you sing a soda bottle as a microphone -
in front of the fish restaurant.
-Did you have a restaurant?
I didn't grow up wealthy.
But our family liked one.
Of course.
There was also
entertainment agency business card.
According to it, 50 million won
would make you successful.
You earned 50 million
in a suspicious manner.
You were at work
in fertilizer and chemical plants.
You earned 5 to 10 million each.
They didn't look like a monthly salary.
-Large sums.
I didn't work in fertilizer factories.
I handled problematic waste.
Like cadmium?
Auto in removing them.
I was kind of their sidekick.
You were there
in illegal waste removal.
These terms are scary.
Isn't that a punishable act?
-Necessarily.
As you can see,
The singer signed the contract.
-Really?
It was with the casino,
but the conditions were bad for him.
He had to perform around the clock,
and the casino is always open.
I speak from experience,
because I was a singer myself.
It violates labor laws.
If you always have to sing,
must be furious.
Did he know anything about you?
-I want to ask the same thing.
Maybe this was the reason.
What is it?
Wife Hwang.
He wrote:
"You belong to a bigger stage."
He meant the casino.
You didn't know him, did you?
He is our own leader
Bong-cheon Kim's wife.
Was she your sugar mama?
- Outrageous.
Don't make it suspicious.
Wake up outside, please.
Sorry.
What do you think you're doing?
-And not.
Smoking inside is illegal.
He didn't cry.
-I can see it.
I didn't smoke.
-Does your throat hurt?
Bad air in the casino
affected his lungs.
Do you have asthma?
- It isn't.
Let me continue.
-Sorry.
I was working at Gazi's night club,
when Wife Hwang hired me at the casino.
"Maybe sugar mama."
-So.
Let's continue.
-Then?
"If you get caught, I'll shoot you."
What?
- He is threatened with a gun.
What did you do?
- Please explain.
Did you get caught with the Wife?
He acted like you, Detective.
Manager Kim thought,
that there was something between us.
I was a singer who loved music,
and the Wife just admired my voice.
Here is an important piece of evidence.
I glanced at Singer Kim's phone.
You wanted to go to Las Vegas.
Director Kim didn't let you -
and ordered to work until the 8th.
According to the appendix -
you had an audition in las vegas,
but the manager refused it
without telling you.
Really?
A person named La Vega heard my song.
Audition was supposed to be just a formality,
but the manager interfered.
He grabbed a business card -
and demanded to see the offers
because of my contract.
I didn't know about the audition song,
and my chance to get to the USA disappeared.
Didn't it feel like the end of the world?
It was your dream.
One more thing.
- More?
Enough.
- Jukra.
I saw your seafood restaurant's account book,
which you kept.
The restaurant bought small quantities of fish,
4,000 to 11,000 won per fish.
You bought in large quantities
From the Merikrot fishery.
Does it sound familiar?
-Sea grouse Jang's fish farm?
According to the information, hundreds of fish were bought -
at unusually low prices.
Really?
-Yes.
I didn't keep a record.
I remember the fish coming
unusually cheap.
My parents were excited,
and the restaurant flourished for a while.
Were they from the Merikrot company?
-What?
Are your parents fishermen?
- Answer me.
Are your parents in the fishing business?
They aren't.
- Don't they?
Let it be.
-Clear.
I examined two people today.
More?
-Mayor.
Me?
You got the glee olympics here.
That's a great achievement.
Did you beat it?
-Yes.
A hilarious sporting event?
-So.
Hence the "Glee Olympics".
- Great.
That's a great achievement.
Do you hope it will help you become president?
-Of course.
I found the casino development agreement.
Manager Kim had to pay
monthly payment for the plot.
Do we take it on the 8th of every month?
Yes.
-8. day?
The days read "Bong".
So.
-How many days is it now?
It's the 8th day now.
-So.
I will receive a cash payment today.
Really?
-Yes.
Can you get it in cash?
A political career requires a lot of money.
Was it a donation?
Forced donation?
-Yes.
On Bong-cheon's phone
is their messages.
"Rude little shit."
Did you know about this?
- Did he save my number like that?
Yes.
-"Rude little shit."
That hurts deeply.
This is important.
Madam Mayor -
ordered the manager to develop the casino
to the site of the landfill.
You agreed to cash payments
always on the 8th.
Exactly.
He asked you to the vault,
which was guarded and bulletproof.
Soundproof and bulletproof.
-So.
Really?
- It's completely sealed.
This is his last message.
The secret of the jeons.
-What?
He believes in prophecies.
Your political choices
were based on predictions.
And to shamanism.
What is it about?
-Really?
Did you see the scrolls in the jewelry box?
One told to grow a flower on the grave,
another spoke of destruction.
On March 27, 2025 -
he had to raise
bigger flower on the grave -
to become king.
To be king?
It refers to the presidency.
Predictions are only indicative.
Would I trust them blindly?
Could you prove it?
I can prove it.
Here they were told to grow a flower.
The casino is shaped like a flower.
Yeah, but it turned out beautiful.
Or what?
What bothered me the most was
that the grave had to be filled with sacrifice.
You know what the grave refers to.
To the landfill.
Does that mean
that someone has to be killed first?
It was a prophecy
which my father got.
Did your father kill someone?
My family has known
shaman Myeong Long blade.
We ask the shaman
predictions every now and then.
When my father built a landfill site,
the employee had an accident.
After hearing the prophecy -
my father buried the man's body -
to the plot as a kind of sacrifice.
I don't know more.
To the landfill?
-A working man?
Did he bury the man?
-Yes.
You admitted to the illegal burial of a body.
My father did that, not me.
It's a disgrace to the family.
- Do you blame the deceased?
I was too young to know about it then.
So your father did it.
-So.
I apologize as his daughter.
But the sacrifice made my father's career flourish.
He served four terms.
Then I had to plant a flower on the grave.
My father had given a human sacrifice,
so I thought the place would be suitable for a casino.
I'm asking this.
-So...
So what?
I want to point out
something else from the notebook.
Other people have also received predictions.
We assume he wrote this
that shaman,
and Bong-cheon blackmailed Mayor Jeon
with a picture of a notebook.
How a notebook
ended up with Mayor Jeon?
He could have killed Bong-cheon
and usurps the notebook.
And not.
I didn't kill him.
I secretly stole the notebook.
When you had shot him twice?
-No.
I can't even use a gun.
It's not difficult.
-How does it happen?
How to…
I am completely ignorant.
-Well...
More and more suspicious.
Our mayor admitted the theft.
I couldn't help it.
My dreams were falling apart.
The crimes you admitted to -
would bring you
triple punishment.
But acknowledge my accomplishments.
One more thing.
-Still? What have I done?
The landfill site can be purchased commercially
into use after 30 years.
This landfill was built in 2000.
What year is it now?
It is now 2025.
It hasn't been that long.
- You built a casino before that.
A little too soon.
True, but think now.
-He admits everything.
Think about it.
The plot was ugly,
and residents complained about it.
It smelled.
- I don't know.
I made the decision for the benefit of the city.
Nevertheless -
Destroyed City didn't fit
for the location of the landfill.
Here it says:
"Getting it off the report will help."
So the landfill was built,
when the environmental report was encrypted.
Your father offered a human sacrifice,
and you built a casino on the land
to advance your career.
Exactly.
-But my family...
Despite this murder story -
he deserves the death sentence.
Heoyoung's special status
helped all of you.
People decide that.
-Listen.
Without the casino
Heoyoung would not have been successful.
Are you finished already, Jeweler?
The final blow.
This is going to hurt.
- Madam Mayor.
You commissioned a private investigator
investigate people associated with the landfill.
Who's the private detective?
Jang?
-Yes.
What did you want to find out?
If the notebook predictions
would have come out…
Let's kill everyone?
-Is that why?
Of course not.
I was trying to sort out the mess my father left behind -
with a public apology.
But first I had to know the facts.
Or so.
-Detective.
We need to investigate further
events of the year 2000 -
before the construction of the landfill.
You believe it all started with that.
-So.
Applause for the lady,
who has the wisdom of age.
Please clap.
-Good work.
Wisdom from 50 years.
-The wisdom of a rich woman.
I believe that Mayor Jeon -
is after these attacks
something to say.
That was enough.
- Are we listening to the politician?
First I want to mention the lips.
Did you have to take a picture that close?
His lips.
- They were weird.
The color makes the lips pop
from a penguin's beak.
At first I thought she had been kissed.
Could someone do that?
-But...
What would leave such a mark?
Like a kiss.
- Those lips.
Look at Mrs. Korukauppias.
- He did it.
Did Bong-cheon and the Jeweler kiss?
It didn't happen that way.
You are not serious.
Now I'll move on to Jang the Seagull.
I explored his room.
Me?
-So.
You enjoy cross-dressing.
What?
I found something strange.
-What?
I found in the wardrobe
a woman's dress and uniform.
I also found some camouflage gear.
Wig, sunglasses and marking paste.
It was used to mark playing cards
for cheating.
Did you play in disguise?
You surely know
that card shark success -
depends on invisibility.
The card shark cannot enter the games,
if he is identified.
That's why Jeweler An
didn't see me at the table.
we played together
but you didn't know me for a reason.
Is that why…
- Do you?
He didn't recognize you.
- Crazy.
He was in disguise.
He won all my money.
I played against a woman.
Baby Jang might be one of those,
who looks good as a woman.
How do you change your voice?
There is a device for that.
Is it?
-Wait a minute.
"Full on."
- He didn't lie.
Really genuine.
-And not.
I want to know this.
Why did Director Kim -
promised a reward of 50 million won for you?
Is it a reward?
-So.
Before his employment contract at the casino -
The cormorant was already known to them.
Were you blacklisted?
-I guess so.
He was hired at the casino
thanks to his skill.
I'll tell you about my findings.
Your mentor taught you
the art of disguise.
Don't students always have a mentor?
I found "The Card Shark's Secret Manual".
- Is there one?
It deals with camouflage,
mixing techniques and more.
The manual was written by
a person named Constable Hyeon.
What?
Yes, and I found him
photo and memento.
Ring a bell.
He is dead.
There was a photo of the urn.
-Wait a minute.
Will he take revenge for his mentor?
- Got under the train.
As mentioned earlier,
Jang the cormorant was a fisherman.
Weren't his parents?
-So.
Formerly Constable Hyeon
and learning cards -
he was an ordinary fisherman.
-So.
He was a fisherman.
Which then became a card shark.
He was skilled and caught more and more fish.
He was like that.
The last person,
whom Constable Hyeon met,
was director Bong-cheon Kim.
The boss killed him.
What if he doubted
Hyeon killed by Bong-cheon,
joined the casino under a fake name -
and waited for the right moment to kill?
That's my theory.
All right.
My mentor, Constable Hyeon,
belonged to the police force.
So was he a constable?
-Yes.
In his police work -
he explored
Four Seasons carefully by Jeon.
He dug things carefully.
I found out he was a policeman,
when I saw his notebook.
I thought he was investigating something big
on the day of his disappearance.
I thought so at first.
But when I couldn't
hold him for many days,
I went looking for him.
Clear.
The search led me
To Heoyoung's special city.
I had no proof
leader of Kim's plots,
but my instinct
convinced me I was right.
The police were going to drop the investigation,
so I knew I had to
reveal the truth yourself.
I played Bong-cheon Kim
owned illegal casinos -
and I scrubbed him clean.
Then he wanted me.
I didn't freak out, I just talked to him.
Good look.
-We only live once.
I said to him:
“I'm here
and ready to work for you."
He was happy and welcomed me
welcome with open arms.
Of course.
- That's how I infiltrated the casino.
Clear.
You mean Jang the Sea Grouse
saw Bong-cheon Kim as a man,
who basically killed his father.
-So.
I understand the revenge of the mentor,
but was that all?
He changed from a fisherman
into a vengeful card shark.
Is there still more to the story?
I want to study a person,
about which we know the least.
Doctor.
-So.
I'll tell you quickly,
how he became a chef.
Inspiration.
- I'm curious.
Fascinating.
I found in the box
medical reports.
In the inhabitants of Tuhokaupunki
had health concerns.
Heavy metal concentrations in the blood
were double.
All were diagnosed
just a flu though.
For patients who had ailments
due to heavy metal deposits,
only a diagnosis of flu was given.
And he got to his bank account
three billion won deposit.
From Bong-cheon Kim?
Four Seasons from Jeon?
-No.
Are you blaming your father again?
I swear…
You may not believe
that I didn't know anything about this.
I didn't know.
-Clear. Let's continue.
Politicians say so.
- I believe that at the moment.
I'm not the same as my father.
-The account book shows,
that the money was from Four Seasons Jeon.
The doctor immediately established a clinic with the money.
My own clinic.
Waist, shoulders,
knees and toes clinic.
Even newsreader Park Ji-yoon
was a regular patient.
I saw the photo.
Weird. He has strong bones.
He came to grind his strong bones.
Do I have to tell you?
-Nothing fit.
Shouldn't patient information be kept confidential?
HOPEFULLY THE RIGHT PARK JI-YOON
CAN'T HEAR
He did well
after opening a clinic in Gangdam,
but it changed.
How?
-What happened?
I saw the court's decision.
-What?
The plaintiff suffered a herniated disc
from gambling too much,
but after the Chef cut him
he became paralyzed.
Oh no.
-Goodness.
Due to a serious medical error -
The chef had to pay
five billion in compensation,
and he lost his license.
He took a loan of three billion
to pay for everything.
He came here.
-The money came from Bong-cheon.
Why work in the kitchen?
- I can explain.
I honestly don't know.
He asked to work in the kitchen of the casino,
and I came here.
And I was good at this job.
What are you talking about?
Did you find your calling?
- Crazy.
It wasn't easy for him.
I found signs in the room that
that he was looking for peace
It's from the Fleek Meditation Center.
I studied the brochure more closely.
He said his life was over,
and the source of all misery -
was Bong-cheon Kim.
- Bong-cheon.
He found peace of mind
Cult leader at Nan's place.
What was its name?
Messianic Church.
-So.
-I don't know if he turned,
but he sought guidance
about religion.
I thought it was a football club.
-Vibrate.
You thought it hinted at Messi.
-The body was left out.
What if it is also related
to a religious ritual?
Believe what you want.
-The Messianic Church.
I don't believe
for any of you to investigate further -
manager Kim's phone.
There was his
and messages from Tohelo Ani.
Duffer?
- I read them.
He procured fools for the boss,
such as the manager of a contracting company
and even authorized.
You brought everyone here.
To Bong-cheon.
-Artificial?
Are you barking?
You are the true tohelo of tohelos.
Pull yourself together.
No need to bark.
- I read the messages.
I thought that was it
from someone anonymous.
But they were talking about Jeweler Ani.
"Tohelo" was a nickname.
-I was wrong.
I thought about this too.
-I didn't know.
I found a safe in the manager's office -
Behind the Joker portrait.
When I opened the drawer, there was a box.
A box decorated with jewels.
I found this inside the box.
A gun.
There was a gun.
How did the leader die?
He was shot.
-So.
I found a revolver.
-Was there a gun?
And next to it were two bullets.
They had clearly been shot at something,
for they were twisted.
I unloaded the gun and noticed
that it had been shot twice.
There were four cartridges left.
That's why -
I'm sure with this gun
shot director Kim.
He was shot with his own gun.
So it seems.
We need to find out
who can claim a gun.
I have an answer.
The box had a logo and the letter "A".
-Really?
"A."
What about it?
-Doesn't it refer to the Jeweler?
Eli Korukauppa A.
-Jeweler An.
Do you sell them in your store?
This is an important piece of evidence,
so please explain.
I gave it to him.
-A gun?
So.
Scary woman.
What's so scary about a gun gift?
Do you sell guns in your store?
Did I give up the gun just because
that i sell them you jerk?
I bought the gun as a gift for him.
You are frustrating.
-Why a gun?
Why a gun?
-Well, what do you think?
Why is a gun needed?
So he can be killed later?
-Yes.
I gave the gun to kill him.
I thought if I let it,
i see where he keeps it.
And not.
Did you kill him?
I couldn't.
Some fool got there first.
Someone else knew the gun was there, too.
Clear.
- We will investigate this further.
And then this.
I didn't find out
what the Jeweler did before.
Don't you?
He was an official.
Really?
-Yes.
He was working at the Ministry of the Interior.
I found the contract between you and the manager.
You had to pay five million,
when residents move.
-Compensation.
You agreed to pay a million
and you shared the rest with the manager.
You are right.
-So.
You are evil.
- Did you take the money?
You signed your contract on May 6, 2002.
The date though
was changed to the 11th.
I must say
that he hated to do
agreements with the manager.
After all, they have a close relationship.
-Why do you say that?
I found it on his phone
messages from 2002.
Manager Kim pressed him
to consider the offer.
Jeweler An rejected her -
and threatened to inform the police.
Was he an uncompromising official?
Which made him change his mind
May 6-11?
When did his sister die?
Do you want my story?
Did you do something for the leader,
when you were in government bread?
My sister always told me to be -
upright and decent.
That's why I banned the manager
not to contact you again.
Then my sister got hit by a car.
I needed money for his surgery.
That's why I changed my mind
and I signed the contract on the 11th.
Or so.
- That's what happened.
Didn't you notice the note in the envelope?
- I don't.
He had to move the residents -
and bury opponents in the landfill.
On the back of the note was the author's name.
Four Seasons Jeon.
-What?
How many messes you made
still have to clean up, dad?
Based on your tone of voice
you could kill your father yourself.
Didn't you know about your father's activities?
Weren't you closely involved?
in building a casino on top of a landfill?
Yes I was.
You seemed to apply
land rezoning.
You planned a stadium instead of a casino.
Because of the Joy Olympics.
Absolutely.
The mayor signed the paper,
but Manager Kim threw it on the floor.
That's why I suggested moving the casino.
I promised to forget about the rent.
For the casino to move?
-So.
Would you give it up?
The stadium does not fit in other cities.
Where would he go?
- The stadium is coming here.
To the casino grounds.
-So.
Joy Olympics
are of course more important.
The mayor and predictions.
This cannot be taken lightly.
He firmly believed,
that his father won four elections
thanks to the predictions.
Predictions of his own
at the time of his candidacy -
were therefore even more important to him.
He concentrated
to a bigger goal, the stadium.
Bong-cheon Kim was in the way
and blackmailed him with a notebook,
so she definitely wanted to get rid of him.
His father buried a man,
so he believed he could kill.
I found the manager in the study
conclusive evidence.
Did anyone notice the button on the floor?
I didn't notice.
There was a button.
It was related to the board,
which covered the secret compartment.
Did it fall from the gun applicant?
It fell out of the gun
when applying or returning,
for it was by the safe.
Let's check the shirt.
Different color.
The button was black.
- It looked like a button on a man's suit.
Jang the cormorant.
So!
-Show me your coat.
Put your hands up.
Hands up or they'll be crushed!
Don't now. Must blood be shed?
How many buttons?
- One is missing.
There are only two here.
Is bloodshed necessary?
Bring the game.
So the button belongs to you.
What were you going to do with the gun?
- I'll tell.
I planned too -
killing me -
By Bong-cheon Kim.
I planned it.
- I guessed.
I knew where the gun was kept.
It went like this.
He went on a rampage and blamed the game
as a scam at 22:05.
A jeweler?
-So.
You finally figured out the scam.
The game was stopped at around 22:10.
I was dressed as a woman,
so I went to the wash
and changing clothes.
The casino's one-year anniversary was coming up,
and the boss would take care of the payments,
so I decided to carry out my plan.
I went to his office
around 10:55 p.m.
I took the gun to kill him there.
He handled the payments
every 7th of the month at 11pm.
The jeweler knew it.
So.
-Casino payment split?
He took care of them himself.
I waited but he didn't come.
He was not seen by 11:10 p.m.,
when I heard someone calling him.
There was someone at the door. I knew I was in trouble.
Who was that?
-Did you see?
I didn't see, but he asked the manager.
Man or woman?
-Did you hear a cough?
It was a man.
- A man?
Exactly.
Was that you?
That was me.
Why…
- Are you kidding me?
There was only one door in the room.
You would have bumped into each other.
Another door leads to the stage.
I thought it wasn't a good day
kill him
so i put the gun back.
I didn't see anything else then.
There were no spent cartridges.
Right?
-No.
The murder happened after that.
-Clear.
Singer, why did you go there at 23:10?
I wanted to meet the manager.
-Why?
I was feeling bad.
I took the medicine and fell asleep.
I woke up to a DM.
I went to ask the manager about the situation.
But in the study…
It was about a dream.
-Didn't you see him?
You don't.
- I don't.
Where was the manager?
Someone had to see him.
Jeweler An.
So.
-What?
Jeweler An.
-So?
Why did you rage?
The lost sums were worthless to you.
I knew he handled the payments then.
-Are you that close?
Only I didn't know.
- I am a VVIP guest.
Like he's not a tohelo.
- I was going to do that.
He knows everything.
- I let myself be taken advantage of.
I had decided to kill him on the 7th.
Mayor Jeon,
you arrived at around 9:40 p.m.
You were furious.
-So.
Yes. There were people on the third floor,
so i asked for the manager
to his study at 9:50 p.m.
How many did you leave?
- At 10 p.m.
You talked for 10 minutes.
-So.
It was a sign to rage at the gaming table.
I did so at 22:05.
The game was suspended at 22:10.
-So.
At 22:10 Bong-cheon offered -
to show me the vault.
Did you go there?
We went to see it.
Did you go inside?
The joker board is in the blind spot.
I was going to open the safe,
take a gun and shoot him.
But he suddenly asked me to the vault too.
I was going to surprise him,
but he told me to go first.
I thought the moment was not right for killing.
I gave up on the idea and left at 10:30 p.m.
The day didn't even fit.
We must keep this in mind
as the investigation continues.
I noticed the manager's room
and cleaning tools between the pallets.
Instructions were attached to the cart.
There was an inscription from the hill -
behind the casino.
-I noticed it.
As the carcasses rot,
accumulating methane gas
may catch fire.
It is likely
that the site of the former landfill -
made gas-related
accidents are possible.
The chef found information about it.
Let's hear him.
-Good.
Clear.
- Good job, Singer.
You spoke clearly even when you were unwell.
But you could put on a mask.
Goodness.
I'm Chef Jang.
The killer murdered the victim
and left the body on display.
Did the victim fall on stage,
or was he taken there?
I believe the victim was
crippled even before that.
He was shot twice on stage.
It was that easy.
But this is strange.
I concluded that he was shot on stage.
The gun does not have a silencer.
Didn't anyone hear the shots?
Everyone should have heard them.
-The vault is soundproof.
But the body was not found in the vault.
Don't forget that
that the body might be moved.
Who among us visited the vault?
Did you go?
-Jeweler.
So.
Mayor Jeon, you visited the vault
requesting your payment.
I will get it in cash the next day.
Only Bong-cheon Kim's voice opens the vault.
-So.
Can't find the answers there?
I would also like to remind
that there was a gas alarm next to the stage.
However, it doesn't work.
I couldn't turn it on,
so i opened it.
One of the three batteries was missing.
Someone deleted it.
-So.
Someone removed it beforehand -
to release gas.
-So.
There is a ventilation duct next to it.
Gas can pass through it.
If gas leaked through it,
and the warning did not work,
he would have lost consciousness suddenly.
That would be possible.
I found an envelope -
Inside jeweler Ani's desk.
It had an environmental report.
According to it, a dump
had caused trouble in the neighborhood -
with high levels of pollution.
That's why many locals
was heavy metal poisoning.
A lot of fish also died.
-So.
There were enough warning signs.
Because of the environmental report -
Rehti An led the demonstration
when representing a group of citizens.
The start-up was a custom job.
- He was assassinated.
In the photos of the demonstration
there is a man next to her.
Who?
- It was…
Who was that?
It was Bong-cheon Kim.
-Absolutely.
Jeweler Armas Bong-cheon
is also in the picture.
Listen up.
-Beyond belief.
Do not assume rashly,
that only Four Seasons
was involved in Rehti Ani's death.
Four Through Jeon's Commandments
realized by Bong-cheon Kim.
So.
-He is directly related to Rehdi's death.
Well said.
-Jeweler An knew it.
I will say this
due to the landfill blacklist.
Rehti An was at the top of the list.
And the list has a signature,
which belonged to Four Seasons Jeon.
So…
- That's right, dad.
All of you -
was a strong motive
leader to kill Kim.
And then the landfill.
You all join the dump
in some way.
So.
-But why the killer -
put the body on display?
Who knew about the gun? I didn't know.
How about you, Singer?
-I was threatened with a gun.
So.
- So I knew about the gun,
but I didn't know where it was stored.
I focused on the gun on my temple.
I didn't know.
I knew.
These two knew about the gun.
He gave it.
Three knew about the gun, two didn't.
Tough vote.
1. VOTING ROUND
THE DETECTIVE GIVES TWO VOICES,
AFTER THE FIRST DISCUSSION
First of all -
he destroyed the Singer's dream.
From Chef Jang
came under the casino.
It had been difficult for him too.
In Nirvana.
-The jeweler wanted to avenge his sister,
A seal because of his mentor.
Then there's the woman who soon finds out,
can he become president.
No one else is chasing something
just as desperately.
I can't be sure…
WHO WILL THE DETECTIVE VOTE FOR?
HE CHOOSE HIS JEWELERS
I couldn't do anything else.
I'm not surprised.
- Neither do I.
The evidence…
You suspect me because of my family member.
-Exactly.
It's poetic.
-What?
Gives a gun as a gift
and shoots the recipient with it.
The message was:
"I will shed as much of your blood—
like being dumped in a landfill."
Right-minded.
Be quiet now. Let's continue.
If my accusation makes you nervous,
use emotion to search for clues.
But let's think together.
Let's get back to the place.
-That sounds good.
Let's catch the killer.
CRIME SCENE REVEALS THE PERPETRATOR
I explored places I couldn't explore.
Let's see.
This place should be checked first.
How do we get to the vault?
BONG-CHEON KIM'S VAULT IS LOCKED
How do we get there?
"Activate voice recognition to confirm."
My name is Bong-cheon Kim.
Open the door.
Doesn't help.
Do you have the boss's voice saved?
INVESTIGATION OF CHEF JANG'S ROOM
What is this?
SOMETHING WAS FOUND UNDER THE MATTRESS
“Kitchen Master Jangin
witch soup recipe."
What the hell?
What is this thing?
Who is this man?
Watch out for him, Detective.
He is dangerous.
-Who?
A chef?
- He's dangerous.
Chef.
-Goodness.
What is this?
RECIPES FROM MASTER JANG
"Cut the fingers into suitable pieces.
Chop the thigh meat into bite-sized pieces.
Neat belly meats.
Punch holes in the flesh if it resists."
He adds fingers to the soup -
and thigh meat in salad.
Why do you add fingers to food?
-What?
It can't be true.
-Why thigh meat in soup?
Why such a salad?
NIGHT
Did you start cooking people?
A CULT FREAK WHO COOKS PEOPLE?
It can't be true.
Please explain this.
"Clean belly meat."
Bong-cheon Kim had a big stomach.
"Put holes in the flesh if it resists."
Is that why two holes?
- I'll take one.
It leaks from the same places as the body.
Looks like a dead person
especially around the stomach.
Head and shoulder.
- They are identical.
I wondered why the body was on display.
Now I know.
Look at the shoulder, the head and the blood.
He is the most suspicious.
Subtitles: Kati Karvonen